I've been given a lot of health advice.
Keep in mind I went to school for
kinesiology. So, without question, the
best is seek professional help. That has
helped me recover from surgeries. That
has saved me from skin cancer, kept me
healthy for all these years, and has
fixed my eye mites. No matter who you
are, whether you're a 17-time world
champion, whether you're like my mom
driving a school bus, whether you're
like my brother framing houses, we all
are worried about our own personal
health. And [music] I think it's very
important to know that you're not
indestructible, you're not alone, and
you're not perfect. And anytime you
[music] have an ailment, asking for help
is not a weakness, it's a strength. And
seeking professional help is
>> [music]
>> a great conduit to being cured or
diminishing your conditions.